buyam.com.ng 2014-02-09

# Privacy Notice | Buyam

Buyam.com.ng knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. **By visiting Buyam.com.ng, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

  * [What Personal Information About Customers Does Buyam.com.ng Gather?](http://www.buyam.com.ng/privacy.html#personal)
  * [What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Websites?](http://www.buyam.com.ng/privacy.html#thirdParty)

### What Personal Information About Customers Does Buyam.com.ng Gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalise and continually improve your shopping experience at Buyam.com.ng. Here are the types of information we gather.

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you.
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Buyam.com.ng or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Buyam.com.ng on other Web sites.
  * **E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Buyam.com.ng if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your Customer Communication Preferences.
  * **Information from Other Sources:** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

### What About Cookies?

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide features such Recommended for You, personalized advertisements on other Web sites (e.g., Buyam Associates with content served by Buyam.com.ng and Web sites using Checkout by Buyam payment service), and storage of items in your Shopping Cart between visits.
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Buyam.com.ng's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Buyam.com.ng products and services that require you to Sign in.

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below and with subsidiaries Buyam.com.ng, Inc. controls that either are subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice.

  * **Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control:** We work closely with affiliated businesses. In some cases, such as Marketplace sellers, these businesses operate stores at Buyam.com.ng or sell offerings to you at Buyam.com.ng. In other cases, we operate stores, provide services, or sell product lines jointly with these businesses. You can tell when a third party is involved in your transactions, and we share customer information related to those transactions with that third party.
  * **Third-Party Service Providers:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
  * **Promotional Offers:** Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of Buyam.com.ng customers on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address.
  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise). Also, in the unlikely event that Buyam.com.ng, Inc., or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
  * **Protection of Buyam.com.ng and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Buyam.com.ng, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice.
  * **With Your Consent** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

### How Secure Is Information About Me?

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
  * We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

### What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Websites?

Our site includes third-party advertising and links to other Web sites. We do not provide any personally identifiable customer information to these advertisers or third-party Web sites. 

These third-party Web sites and advertisers, or Internet advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to send (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our Web site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other features that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party Web sites are not covered by this Privacy Notice. Please contact them directly for more information about their privacy practices. In addition, the Network Advertising Initiative offers useful information about Internet advertising companies (also called "ad networks" or "network advertisers"), including information about how to opt-out of their information collection. 

Buyam.com.ng also displays personalized third-party advertising based on personal information about customers, such as purchases on Buyam.com.ng, visits to Buyam Associate Web sites, or use of payment services. Although Buyam.com.ng does not provide any personal information to advertisers, advertisers (including ad-serving companies) may assume that users who interact with or click on a personalized advertisement meet their criteria to personalise the ad (for example, users in the Southern States who bought or browsed for umbrellas and raincoats).

### Which Information Can I Access?

Buyam.com.ng gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with Buyam.com.ng for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. The information you have access to and can update will change as our Web site evolves.

### What Choices Do I Have?

  * As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of such Buyam.com.ng features as Your Profile, Wish Lists, and Customer Reviews.
  * You can add or update certain information on certain pages. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.
  * The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. Additionally, you can disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the Web site of its manufacturer. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of Buyam.com.ng's essential features, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block or otherwise reject our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Cart, proceed to Checkout, or use any Buyam.com.ng products and services that require you to Sign in.

### Are Children Allowed to Use Buyam.com.ng?

Buyam.com.ng does not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use Buyam.com.ng only with the involvement of a parent or guardian. 

### Does Buyam.com.ng Participate in the Safe Harbor Program?

Buyam.com.ng is a participant in the Safe Harbor program developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Union. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles agreed upon by the U.S. and the E.U. For more information about the Safe Harbor and to view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor Web site. If you would like to contact Buyam.com.ng directly about the Safe Harbor program, please send an e-mail to safeharbor@Buyam.com.ng. 

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit Buyam.com.ng, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington. If you have any concern about privacy at Buyam.com.ng, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers. 

### Examples of Information Collected

#### Information You Give Us

You provide most such information when you search, buy, bid, post, participate in a contest or questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; place an order through Buyam.com.ng or one of our third-party sellers; provide information in Your Account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us) or Your Profile; communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire or a contest entry form; compile Wish Lists or other gift registries; provide employer information when opening a corporate account; participate in Discussion Boards or other community features; provide and rate Reviews; specify a Special Occasion Reminder; share information with Buyam Friends; and employ other Personal Notification Services, such as Available to Order Notifications. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; e-mail addresses of Buyam Friends and other people; content of reviews and e-mails to us; personal description and photograph in Your Profile; and financial information.

#### Automatic Information

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform; purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create features such as Purchase Circles and Top Sellers; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call our support or free phone number. We may also use browser data such as cookies, Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our Web site for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

#### Information from Other Sources

Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily; account information, purchase or redemption information, and page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses or for which we provide technical, fulfillment, advertising, or other services; search term and search result information from some searches conducted through the Web search features offered Alexa Internet and A9.com; search results and links, including paid listings (such as Sponsored Links).

#### Information You Can Access

Examples of information you can access easily at Buyam.com.ng include up-to-date information regarding recent orders; personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, password, communications and personalized advertising preferences, and address book); payment settings (including credit card information and gift certificate, gift card, and check balances); e-mail notification settings (including Alerts, Available to Order notifications, Delivers, Recommended for You, and newsletters); recommendations (including recent product view history, prior order history, and Favourites); shopping lists and gift registries (including Wish Lists and Baby and Wedding Registries); Marketplace seller accounts; and Your Profile (including your product Reviews, Requests, and Recommendations, "So You'd Like to..." guides, personal profile, people you tagged as interesting, and Buyam Friends).
